riffynetwork.com 2019-06-14

# Privacy Notice : Air Jordan 1, Mens Air Jordans Cheap

We takes seriously of customers' privacy security! Thus here we promise to provide a safe online experience for all our users. This policy applies to information collected online through our website. Please read the flowing privacy policy below and contact us if you have any questions.

Account Creation and Registration

When you make a purchase at our website, you will have the option to create an account. By creating an account, the system will remember your personal and purchase information. This results in a more express checkout process for future purchases that will be fast, easy and always completely secure. You are not required to create an account in order to checkout.

Creating an account will enable you to access specific information such as your order history and enable you to update past purchase addresses and information. At all times, your personal information is accessible for you to review, edit, or update as necessary by clicking on the "My Account" link. This information is the property of our website and we do not sell or share any information with third parties unless otherwise specifically indicated. 

Collected Customer's Information

We collect information to process your order. We collect personally identifiable information such as names, email addresses. We also may collect your IP address, domain name, access times and referring website address. This information is collected both during registration on a page or in response to specific requests, for example when signing up for a newsletter. Information collected in our website will be available within hosts of We to process your order. P.S. If you would wish to delete your privacy information at online, please contact us after the order completes. We will deal with it within 24 hours.

Security

Our website is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. State-of-the-art technology protects your data from unauthorized third parties. Our website uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software to protect your data and secure your transactions. SSL encrypts all your personal information, including your credit card number, name and address during transactions. This provides a safe, secure shopping environment. Only parties responsible for processing your order have access to your credit card and bank information. In addition, our website ensures added security by providing increased encryption on all our servers to prevent data mining and server attacks.

Using Cookies

Our website uses cookies to deliver specific content to our customers which we believe they will enjoy. Cookies are web enabled pieces of software stored on a customer's computer used to identify certain users and offer customized content. All cookies on our site are in no way linked to any personally identifiable information.

Aggregate Information

Aggregate information is occasionally shared with the partners of our website to plan advertising or promotions. We only share with our partners non-personal, aggregate statistical information regarding customers, sales, traffic patterns, and site usage. Our website does not share any personally identifiable information.

Updates to This Policy

By using this web site, you consent to the collection and use of certain information by our website. All changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page or our home page so the customer is always aware of the information we collect and how we use it. The information in this policy can change at anytime and we encourage all customers to review this policy as often as necessary.

Consent

By using our website, you're agreeing to let us collect and use your information as we describe in this Privacy & Security Policy. If we change our policies, we will post any changes on the website, so that you are always informed about what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.
